听力考试正式开始，请看听力部分第一节。第一节。听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题。从题中所给的三个选项中，选出最佳选项。听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。每段对话仅读一遍，例如。现在，你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。你将听到以下内容。你将有五秒钟的时间，将正确答案标在试卷上。衬衫的价格为九磅。十五遍是，所以你选择项，并将其标在试卷上。现在，你有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容。
Have you seen the movie Hangover?
We went to see it last night.
How was it?
Jason thought it was extremely amusing, but I was a bit disappointed.
Susan, I heard you are going to France.
How long will you be staying there?
A whole year.
My aunt lives there.
I'm going to do a one -month course at a language school and spend the rest of the
time traveling. Let's see what drinks you've got for the party tonight.
Everything. wine, soft drinks like Coke, 7 you name it, I've got it.
Have you ordered the cake?
Of course. I don't have a library card.
Do I need one?
You have to have one, only to take books out.
You're okay if you just sit in one of rooms reading.
Well then, I'll just read here.
Thank you. I wish I knew the times of the trains to London, but our phone's out of
order. Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll find out for you on the Internet.
Thank you. Excuse me, I wonder if you could tell me how to find a place to have my
第一节到此结束。第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。每段对话或独白后。有几个小题。从题中所给的三个选项中，选出最佳选项。听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小。小题，每小题五秒钟。听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。每段对话或独白读两遍听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
shoes mended. I'm new in town.
Ah, there is a good shop not far from here.
Go straight ahead and walk about three blocks.
I can't remember the name of the shop, but you'll find it.
It's near the police station.
By the way, you know about the town guide?
It's a thin book and has all kinds of useful information.
You'll find one in any bookstore.
Thanks a lot.
You've been so helpful.
Let's see, did you say the repair shop was three blocks away from here?
Exactly. Thanks again.
Excuse me, I wonder if you could tell me how to find a place to have my shoes
mended. I'm new in town.
Ah, there is a good shop not far from here.
Go straight ahead and walk about three blocks.
I can't remember the name of the shop, but you'll find it.
It's near the police station.
By the way, you know about the town guide?
It's a thin book and has all kinds of useful information.
You'll find one in any bookstore.
Thanks a lot.
You've been so helpful.
Let's see, did you say the repair shop was three blocks away from here?
Exactly. Thanks again.
听下面一段对话，回答第八和第九两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
I've been here many times.
There are quite a lot of delicious dishes to choose from.
What are you thinking of ordering?
Well, I haven't decided yet.
What are you going to order?
I think I'll have the roast chicken.
They really make it well here.
I had roast chicken yesterday when I ate out with Shelley.
Their beef steak is good too.
You can have it served with beans and mushrooms.
But I'm not that hungry.
Is the fried fish or the seafood salad good?
Never had them before.
Maybe if you get the steak, we could share.
That sounds like a good idea.
I've been here many times.
There are quite a lot of delicious dishes to choose from.
What are you thinking of ordering?
Well, I haven't decided yet.
What are you going to order?
I think I'll have the roast chicken.
They really make it well here.
I had roast chicken yesterday when I ate out with Shelley.
Their beef steak is good too.
You can have it served with beans and mushrooms.
But I'm not that hungry.
Is the fried fish or the seafood salad good?
Never had them before.
Maybe if you get the steak, we could share.
That sounds like a good idea.
听下面一段对话。回答第十至第十二三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Hello, Mr. White.
Do you think it's possible for us to talk some time today?
I'd love to, Ms.
Wilson, but I've got a pretty tight schedule today.
I've got to finish reading the yearly financial report by 10.
Then I have to drive to the airport to pick up an advertiser at 11.
After that, I'll have a meeting with him over lunch.
Can I see you after lunch?
Well, let me see.
After lunch, I have to attend a senior staff meeting, which may last about two
hours. Can you come at three?
We can talk for an hour before I meet my sales team at four.
I'm afraid an hour is too short.
What about tomorrow morning?
9 to 11, then.
I'll wait for you at the office.
Okay. See you then.
Hello, Mr. White.
Do you think it's possible for us to talk some time today?
I'd love to, Ms.
Wilson, but I've got a pretty tight schedule today.
I've got to finish reading the yearly financial report by 10.
Then I have to drive to the airport to pick up an advertiser at 11.
After that, I'll have a meeting with him over lunch.
Can I see you after lunch?
Well, let me see.
After lunch, I have to attend a senior staff meeting, which may last about two
hours. Can you come at three?
We can talk for an hour before I meet my sales team at four.
I'm afraid an hour is too short.
What about tomorrow morning?
9 to 11, then.
I'll wait for you at the office.
Okay. See you then.
听下面一段对话，回答第十三至第十六四个小题。现在你有二十秒钟的时间。阅读这四个小题。
Hey, I hear they're going to send you to Germany for the new project.
Boy, news travels fast around here.
I only got the orders a couple of hours ago.
Rachel doesn't even know.
Oh, no? So what are you waiting for?
When do you plan to tell her?
Well, she's at work at the moment.
She doesn't finish until five.
I'll have to wait until tonight now, I suppose.
Well, I was posted there before, back in 2008.
It's okay. A bit like England, really.
At least the weather's similar, and the people aren't much different.
The only thing I didn't like is the food, especially the sausages.
What do you intend to do about the family?
Are you going to take them with you?
Well, I'd like to, but I don't know much about the situation at the moment.
You know, about schools and all that.
But I hope to move the family out there in a couple of months' time.
I don't think I want to a year and a half out there on my own.
I mean, without Rachel and the kids.
I mean, I don't see that much of them now as it is.
Yeah, well, that's the way it is normally in our company, I suppose.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Let me pay for the coffee.
No, no, I'll pay.
Hey, Bill, I hear they're going to send you to Germany for the new project.
Boy, news travels fast around here.
I only got the orders a couple of hours ago.
Rachel doesn't even know.
Oh, no? So what are you waiting for?
When do you plan to tell her?
Well, she's at work at the moment.
She doesn't finish until five.
I'll have to wait until tonight now, I suppose.
Well, I was posted there before, back in 2008.
It's okay. A bit like England, really.
At least the weather's similar, and the people aren't much different.
The only thing I didn't like is the food, especially the sausages.
What do you intend to do about the family?
Are you going to take them with you?
Well, I'd like to, but I don't know much about the situation at the moment.
You know, about schools and all that.
But I hope to move the family out there in a couple of months' time.
I don't think I want to a year and a half out there on my own.
I mean, without Rachel and the kids.
I mean, I don't see that much of them now as it is.
Yeah, well, that's the way it is normally in our company, I suppose.
Yeah, well, we'll see.
Let me pay for the coffee.
No, no, I'll pay.
听下面一段独白，回答第十七至第二十四个小题。现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Hello, everyone. Welcome to our program.
I'm Jenny Jackson.
The weather here in Juarez has become unbearable.
With no rains for over a year, the city is suffering from unusually hot weather.
Some light showers have been forecast since last month, but all of them have been
effective in surrounding areas.
Summer has not even started yet, but temperatures have reached 40 degrees centigrade
in the past three days, and people have been warned not to go out of their homes,
not if you walk on foot at least, between 11 in the morning and 7 in the evening.
Little kids and the elderly are the ones who have suffered the most from this
extreme heat wave.
must drink water all the time.
To help our audience have a better understanding of this extreme weather,
we have invited Professor Torres from University of Mexico to our studio this
evening. Hello, everyone.
Welcome to our program.
I'm Jenny Jackson.
The weather here in Juarez has become unbearable.
With no rains for over a year, the city is suffering from unusually hot weather.
Some light showers have been forecast since last month, but all of them have been
effective in surrounding areas.
Summer has not even started yet, but temperatures have reached 40 degrees centigrade
in the past three days, and people have been warned not to go out of their homes,
not if you walk on foot at least, between 11 in the morning and 7 in the evening.
Little kids and the elderly are the ones who have suffered the most from this
extreme heat wave.
They must drink water all the time.
To help our audience have a better understanding of this extreme weather,
we have invited Professor Torres from University of Mexico to our studio this
evening. from Thank you.
第二节到此结束。现在，你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
听力部分到此结束。